makeuseofandroid.com 2013-05-11

# Privacy Policy ~ Make Use Of Android

  * **Make Use Of Android respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Make Use Of Android.

  * **Credit card details**

Make Use Of Android will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Make Use Of Android.

  * **External Sites.**

Make Use Of Android is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

  * **Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Make Use Of Android and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Make Use Of Android have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.   
Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.  
For any other information email [webmaster](mailto:makeuseofandroid@gmail.com)

  * **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
